<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James P. Conroy</title>
    <description>James Conroy&#39;s open source portfolio
</description>
    <link>https://you.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://you.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 14:25:57 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 14:25:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why you should hire me!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, when you’re looking for someone to hire you have plenty of options. I know, I used to hire people all of the time and took a lot for someone to stand out in the crowd. You know, like writing a blog post on why you should hire me. As I said, there are many reasons, here’s just a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im-a-full-stack-developer-with-a-diverse-background&quot;&gt;1. I’m a full-stack developer with a diverse background&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/jameslookingcool.png&quot; alt=&quot;James looking cool&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now have a background in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Ruby, Ruby on Rails … you get the point. But, prior to learning all of that I worked for a startup that grew out of its startup phase while I was there. In addition to hiring I was involved with operations (like making sure the internet was working, which is harder than you might think), real estate (yea, I had to find us new office space), product management (I started our graphic design department and various features for clients), and client interaction (like, you know, getting on a plane to see a client in Minnesota in winter).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;i-take-great-selfies&quot;&gt;2. I take great selfies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/santaselfie.png&quot; alt=&quot;Santa Hawaii Selfie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See that picture up there. That’s from Christmas day and I was in Hawii.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, so it was my honeymoon, but still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im-really-motivated&quot;&gt;3. I’m REALLY motivated&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/hoynehouse.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hoyne&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yea, that’s my house. I recently bought it and, since it’s about 120 years old, it needs A LOT of work. Want to know if I’m going to work hard and show up on time? I gotta make those mortgage payments!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seriously, I’m a hard worker and a quick study.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 10:00:07 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://you.github.io/blog/2015/06/30/Why_you_should_hire_me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://you.github.io/blog/2015/06/30/Why_you_should_hire_me.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
